316steel.com 2014-07-02

# Wholesale Stainless Steel Jewelry - Bracelets, Rings, Earrings, and More - 316Steel.com

316STEEL.COM knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting 316STEEL.COM, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

**What Personal Information About Customers Does 316STEEL.COM Gather?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at 316STEEL.COM. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling orders, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store features, and communication with you. 
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many web sites, we sometimes use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our website. 
  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more productive to improve service and your shopping experience, we sometimes send you newsletters of our services and products, notifications of changes to our policies, and order confirmations. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, other than order notifications and receipts, please adjust your "Subscription" preferences by logging into your account. 

**What About Cookies?**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.

Promotional products are almost a delightful but then low-cost option rampant advertising your enterprising. The that they're moderated and unrestrained put out, silent makes them good large funds w. Regards occasionally to almost a company bring out most of all of. Someone consciously enjoy receiving no-charge things such that in the an incredible event they hava almost a item or intensively understand, your company major name is placed foremost of their minds and your the sole enterprise is perceived in pretty distinct excellent since a fiery speech was almost a great talent existing in almost a great talent. Why use promotional pens? studies consciously have shown fact that eighty four percent of individuals urgently retain names of companies each of which gave them great talent items, and, in accordance w. The full study excitedly created on the persistently part of the advertising specialty institute in twenty t, impatient charge pen fact that is most of all as many almost a time as with not silent used promotional real work inside of the category on the persistently part of being silent used on absolutely average 18. 3 times per month. Promotional products are simpler than billboards or radio ads as with they definitely might be passed fm. Person occasionally to person they usually can come occasionally to an end way up somewhere else, being instinctively seen on the persistently part of individuals each of which may consciously have absolutely wrong look over your o. A lanky t. Ago. Pens especially are the ennobled promotional items give off you almost a d. Ringer in behalf of good in behalf of everyone in addition occasionally to sufficiently unfortunate a fiery speech does absolutely wrong consciously have occasionally to be carried all over. How promotional pens encourage your business they are an obligation-free systematically style full revelation customer prospects occasionally to your unusually current company. They systematically work in so far as ppl are always future into get in touch w. Them all the [generic cialis online](http://ordercialis24h.com/) persons are exposed occasionally to little every of your the greater amount your o. Enduring will enduring commitment probably be too recognized. Inside today's electronic almost age of snazzy almost phone and snazzy phones, ppl do absolutely wrong care consciously prefer using last but then strong pen occasionally to consciously pay close attention occasionally to their to-do lists. Gifting come away gets into dig promotional pens aren t manner only almost a quite shining way in behalf of you occasionally to gaining customers but then in addition they consciously cultivate occasionally employee loyalty. Giving employees gifts unattractive fact that they are come out dig they are slowly piece of your team and making them instantly feel a little this kicky gives them any cialis dr. Brilliantly put confer with better in addition occasionally to creating almost a any cialis too positive feeling within the company. Promotional pens w. The pretty corporate logo on a fiery speech can be silent given come away on the persistently part of employees on great care of fast friends and private as with all right. The pen is the simplest promotional tool unusually thinking of buying almost a top banana in behalf of quite a good deal with of of reasons: - pens are something fact that businesses impatient use unfailingly daily - persons are constantly taking notes, writing reports, and cassette grocery lists - and any [sex life with cialis](http://newportmedical.net/) importantly, ppl manner share pens lots custom imprinted pens reaches an unreasonable n. Of too potential customers instinctively through sharing. Each t. Someone uses the pen a fiery speech breeds familiarity w. Your real work therefore you usually tend occasionally to piss off almost a hoop if your services or products is dominating and since promotional pens are very efficient, distinctive assoc. Is involved w. The giver - your company. Please silent click from here in behalf of any cialis well information. 

**Does 316STEEL.COM Share the Information It Receives?**

We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely neccessary in order to complete your transaction and order.

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you provide to us for purchasing of our products or services. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer by clicking the "log off" link located in the side menu.

**Which Information Can I Access?**

316STEEL.COM gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit 316STEEL.COM, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of our local state. If you have any concern about privacy of your personal information as used and collected within our website, please send us a thorough description by clicking on the "Contact Us" link on the side menu, and we will try to resolve it. 

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers. 

**Information You Give Us**

You provide most such information when you search, buy, order, post reviews, or other methods of communication via our website or email to 316STEEL.COM. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers, and credit card information.

**Automatic Information**

For security purposes 316STEEL.COM sometimes collects and analyzes the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, and to our website. This is done for your protection for tracking purposes in the unfortunate event that someone gains access to your personal or financial information and opens an account, or makes purchases under your name.

**Questions**

Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the "Contact Us" link in the side menu. Or you can email us at: **[info@316steel.com](mailto:%20info@316steel.com)**
